Delulu means delusion.
Seeing things that don't exist.
What's the Malayalam word
for delusion?
The Malayalam word for delusion...
"Delulu" works.
Actually, it's cute.
You can just call me Delulu
from now on.
- Delulu!
- Delulu...
Can you please stop ordering
all these clothes?
I'm a little short on cash right now.
Let me explain why, Prabha.
I remember every outfit
I used to wear.
But my favourite kurti...
The white one with
lavender flowers on it...
I simply can't wear that one now.
So I thought, maybe I
could wear it if I saw it.
Oh.
Hey...
Can you conjure up
a 500 rupee note?
Hey! I'm not some genie
you summon from a bottle!
I can handle a few simple things.
I have some skills.
Like last week, when that guy acted smart
with you, and I made his bike crash.
Stuff like that.
Which guy?
Sreekuttan?
I don't know his name.
Oh my God!!!
Oh, sorry!
Not God, not God.
Actually, I do remember
certain things about myself.
Like my lifestyle, my habits,
my interests.
But I can't remember
any of the main things.
Like my family,
or my friends...
Nothing at all!
Except for one thing.
What's that?
Right before I died,
someone, somewhere, said "Yes."
It's like someone wanted me to die.
Who was it?
I don't know.
Well... I meant to say this
back at the studio.
You have a beautiful voice, Delulu.
You're gifted.
If you hadn't died...
you would've become a star.
Now that I'm dead,
becoming a star is my only option, right?
"When someone sat close to me at night,
like new-fallen rain in cool delight"
"My heart shifted, lighter than ever,
turning at once to a moonlit river"
"Slowly unfolding its wings
in tender delight"
"Weaving a chain of laughter
pure and bright"
"My mind fills up
on its own tonight"
"Come, let's go to distances
we've never seen"
"Becoming two lovely,
colourful clouds serene"
"In this new birth
where our paths convene"
"Let's find our shelter on a blossom
branch kissed by morning dew"
"Becoming the breath
that rises soft and true"
"Till every painful memory
softens and bids adieu"
Stop!
"From which stretch of sky
did I fall and fly"
"A lost little star
slipping out of the sky?"
"Who else must I search for
as days drift by?"
"I still don't know
the right paths to surmise"
"Yet I carried a deep desire
for a safe haven's rise"
"Which lingered as moisture
gently filling my eyes"
"In all this rush
that surrounds me endlessly"
"Isn't there someone nearby
who cares for me?"
"Even at my lightest mischief,
soft and carefree"
"Doesn't he keep smiling,
happily?"
"Will you join your hands
and shape a swing?"
"If you do, I will step forward with joy
and gently begin to swing"
"When someone sat close to me at night,
like new-fallen rain in cool delight"
"My heart shifted, lighter than ever,
turning at once to a moonlit river"
"Slowly unfolding its wings
in tender delight"
"Weaving a chain of laughter
pure and bright"
"My mind fills up
on its own tonight"
[Astrologer: Krishnanunni Panicker]
So you just want me to visit
the houses you're trying to sell?
Not every one of them, Rupe.
Only the ones where
unnatural deaths have happened.
Yes, houses where notorious murders
have occurred.
And suicides.
Altogether,
I've got nearly 28 such houses
on hold across Kerala.
Will one puja take care
of all of them?
Not like that. First, I will do
an astrological assessment
and then determine
the required remedies.
After that, you just have to
carry them out.
Your learned cousin is the one
who went for the lawyer's
son's puja that day, right?
He's very skilled.
It'd be great if he came too.
No chance!
Prabhendu works only part-time.
He only deals with
cases involving children.
Risky cases like these
are handled by me personally.
Yes, what is it?
I'm looking for the office
of the family court lawyer.
Is it a mutual divorce?
No. I'm okay with it.
But my wife is the one
who wants to end it.
That's something
we can resolve right here.
Still, go meet the lawyer.
- It's the office next door.
- Okay.
So, what about the payment?
What if there's more than one ghost in
those houses where mass murders occurred?
That depends.
We'll even leave some
room for you to negotiate.
If that's the case... err...
a per-head rate for each ghost.
- Isn't it okay?
- Okay.
Okay!
Lord Guruvayurappa!
Just hold this
and give it one pull.
Wow, this is so easy!
Also, no tears wasted.
Thulasi!
Your dad!
Grab Pappu's blue spray
from the kitchen.
Or never mind.
I'll come there.
Okay.
Indutty...
Your dad is coming.
Get going. I'll call you
when lunch is ready.
Huh?!
You're here?
Who is in there then?
It... it...
it's from the speaker, Uncle.
Then how did it stop now?
Oh, really?
Let me check.
Hey, don't pull these kinds of stunts
when I'm not around.
Sorry!
I thought you had grand plans
for cooking today?
What happened?
Finished helping her already?
Well... it's just...
Dad was there with Pappu.
So I just came back inside.
By the way, why aren't you two
talking to each other?
What's the reason?
It's because of Pappu.
What did Pappu do?
Well...
The day my mom passed away...
everyone was here.
It was chaotic,
with all the crying and commotion.
When it was time
to take her body away,
Pappu suddenly started
barking non-stop.
Mom was his favourite person.
He was tied up
in the backyard then.
So I hurried out
and brought him inside.
He deserved to see Mom
one last time, right?
The moment Dad saw him,
he shouted,
"Both of you, get out!"
Dad never liked animals.
He wouldn't even look at Pappu.
I took him and stood outside...
until all the rituals were over.
Dad took away...
the last chance for me
and Pappu...
to be with Mom.
From that day on,
I've barely spoken to him.
And neither has Dad, not since I removed
my sacred thread.
But that was back then, right?
Now you've got
your sacred thread again,
and your Dad is now
Pappu's favourite person.
Then why aren't you two talking?
It's not possible now.
We just… got set that way.
Then just reset it!
Look, Prabha...
staying upset with someone
and holding onto it forever...
it's simply exhausting.
Life's too short for all that!
Hmm.
Point.
Thank you.
Errr...
I'm on the phone, Uncle.
Thulasi has called
us to have lunch.
Come on.
Yes, I'll be there.
I'll tell Indu.
Alright.
- Was that Neelakandan?
- Yes.
Deepu chettan has come home,
along with everyone.
He called to ask if Indu
will attend the temple festival.
Uncle is hesitant
to ask him directly.
Indu had lunch, took his bike,
and went off somewhere.
Is that so?
Uncle...
Has Indu been acting
a little unusual lately?
- Ha! I was just about to ask you that.
- Oh really?
- One thing's certain.
- What?
- He's possessed.
- By a ghost?
Not a ghost!
Possessed by love for a girl!
How do you know?
I caught him red-handed today.
He was whispering away
on the phone.
From the looks of it,
it was definitely a girl
on the other end.
Oh! I had no idea!
There's a lot
you've got no idea about!
Do you even know
all the puja rituals?
Well,
you should've thought of that when
you got your sister married to a cook!
The fact that I made it this far
from that background
is purely because of
my own talent!
That much I'll accept.
Uncle...
I'm thinking of
focusing on exorcisms.
There are families that have been
doing that for generations, Rupe.
To avoid the side effects,
you need the expertise and spiritual energy
passed down through generations.
I'm doing this after proper study.
So I'm not scared.
- Fear is a good thing!
- Huh?!
Fear was the very first emotion
humans ever had...
for basic safety.
I do follow basic safety precautions
when I perform exorcisms.
There are three types of spirits.
Do you know?
Hmm. I don't.
Randukama...
Bhokthukama...
and Handukama.
The first two are relatively harmless.
But the Handukama
comes only to kill!
It won't go back
without taking a life.
Oh god!
Annamma Joseph.
Born in 1932.
Not this one either.
Delulu!
Here's one...
a girl named Tessa.
Born in '88.
Try to remember...
Could your name be Tessa?
No! Born in '88 means
she's over 30!
How old do I look to you?
About twen--
Thirty-thirty two!
What?! I'm not that old!
Are there any other
Mar Thoma churches around here?
Let's see... around here...
If you're a ghost
who's crossed districts,
we might have to check
the Kottayam-Thiruvalla area.
It's alright.
We'll keep looking.
Lillykutty!
I just wish I could at
least remember my name.
Don't worry, Delulu.
We will keep trying.
Won't we, Lillykutty?
- Did you know my grandmother?
- Huh?
I asked whether you
knew my grandmother.
Yes… your grandmother…
I went to her tuition
classes back in eighth grade.
Don't you recognize us?
Yes, I do.
Kalarickal Davis…
the one who lives near the tile factory?
Of course!
Davis Chettan is like family to us!
I am Davis!
Davis Chetta...
Are there any other
new cemeteries nearby?
Cemetery?
There's St. George Cemetery.
I already went there.
Anything else, dear?
Then... there's Paleparambil...
Did you go to Paleparambil Church?
Yeah, I went there too.
There are no other cemeteries.
None, huh?
Hmm, alright then.
Okay, get up.
Let's go.
Okay.
Come on.
You look really beautiful after switching
from that T-shirt to a churidar.
[chanting slokas]
Rupe! Where's Indu?
I brought him.
But he didn't come inside.
Go check on him, Rupe.
Ask him to come and be here.
Okay, Deepu Chetta.
That's Animon for you!
My turn.
Don't miss.
You see that teddy bear? That's the prize.
I need it for my autorickshaw.
Wait and watch!
It didn't pop?
Not even close!
Guess I've lost my teddy bear.
Just a minute.
Psst!
One single shot.
Make it pop, okay?
- Okay.
What?
You called me, didn't you?
Err... it's just...
balloon...
It didn't pop.
- Huh?
- Sorry.
Don't worry.
No one saw it except me.
My prestige is
on the line here, okay?
It has to pop
on the count of three.
Done.
One...
Two...
Sorry!
[Traditional satirical storytelling
performance on stage]
Bless you!
[performance continues]
You stole it already?!
Ugh! No!
I just need one good look
at someone.
I can wear it.
How do I look?
Hmm... not bad.
A little appreciation would be nice.
I have to feel like it, right?
Hey, you!
Over here!
Talking to yourself? Huh?
What?!
I'm on the phone!
So you were lost in that,
weren't you?
Every young prince these days
sleeps and wakes up
with that thing in hand.
Put it away!
Who's this "young prince"?
- Prabhendu.
- Oh.
Indu looks radiant today.
Looks like he's met his maiden.
Indu!
[performance continues]
It's Rupa.
He's probably calling me to the temple.
Come on, let's go!
- Hey!
- Indu!
- Are you leaving?
Hey, Prabha...
your ticket to Bombay has arrived.
For Viraj Trivedi's recording session.
Aren't you coming to Bombay, Delulu?
Of course I am!
Anyway, I've got nothing else
to do here, right?
Hey...
When the flight is
up above the clouds,
will you be tempted
to go to heaven?
I'll save the rest of my laughter
for tomorrow!
Hey, your brother's calling.
Don't pick up!
That'll just bring trouble.
Must be because
I didn't enter the temple.
You're seeing a ghost this close...
Yet, why don't you believe in God?
The answer lies
within the question itself.
It's because I can't see God.
Can you see music, Prabha?
You can only hear music, right?
Yeah, I mean... we can play or sing.
That's just like taking a printout
from a printer.
But what I meant was...
the original source.
Music itself.
Where does music come from?
It's...
It's talent and practice.
Exactly!
Talent is God,
and practice is prayer!
Simple!
Incredible!
A devil is vouching for God!
Don't call me Devil!
I am a nice spirit!
A good soul.
Sorry, sorry!
I'm not entirely convinced
about you either, Delulu.
I keep calming myself down by thinking
you're nothing more than my imagination.
A very powerful and
impactful hallucination.
Oh Jesus!
So you're saying
my skills are worthless?
Ha! Skills?
You're still on a learner's permit!
You tried switching on the light
and blew the bulb!
Can you even touch anyone at all?
Pathetic!
Yes, I can.
Huh?!
This...
This breeze that hit me just now...
That was my touch.
Breeze is the easiest medium
to do that.
A soft breeze.
Give me the phone.
Let me see
if I can take a picture.
Go ahead.
You won't get anything.
Did it work?
Let me try a video.
Hmm.
Did it work now?
You won't see me in it.
Google Pay is risky.
Do you have cash?
Crush it properly,
mix it with water and have it.
Okay bro, thanks.
Huh?
- Hey!
- Where?
What is it?
Wait, we're coming.
Come on.
I'm screwed!
Come on, get up!
Let's go!
What's wrong?
I'll tell you later.
Let's go!
Hello... how high are you...
I mean... Hi... how are you?
What were you filming
on your phone?
No, I wasn't filming you guys!
He'll show it
to the cops, Sreerag.
Didn't we chase this guy off
the other day?
Don't you remember?
Boys, honestly,
I have nothing against you.
Give me your phone.
Don't give it to them, Prabha.
Let me deal with this.
You can check my gallery.
I haven't taken any pictures!
These guys are so rude, Prabha!
Grab the phone from him.
Just be quiet, Delulu!
- Huh?
Hit him, Prabha!
- Idiots!
- Delulu, please!
I can solve this!
What's wrong with this guy?
Just give me the phone, Kiddo.
I don't usually get involved
in things like these.
I don't even know
who you guys are.
How about I let you know?
Alright then.
Okay.
Let's go.
Sreerag...
Hey!
I just...
I got high all of a sudden.
- Is he gone?
- Yeah, perfect!
While you stood there like a tableau,
he walked off with the phone.
Huh? When?
Come on! If we hurry,
we can catch him.
Right!
Are they following us?
- Yes.
- Oh no!
They are just kids, Prabha.
This is bad,
this is really bad!
Stop for a second, Prabha.
Are you planning to spend your
whole life being scared like this?
Are you?
No.
[Song from Ottam Thullal
Kerala Traditional song]
Oh no!
Dude, go get him!
- Where's my bike key?
- Huh?
The bike key, where is it?
Can we talk after this?
Fine, fine.
- Hereafter...
- Hereafter?
- If you ever pull this kind of stunt--
- "on this street again..."
- I'll smash your face--
- "and change its shape," right?
- Yes!
- That's fine, Chetta. No problem.
- Hmm.
- Right.
Scram!
Oh, sorry, Chetta!
- All good?
- Absolutely!
Let's go!
What's the check-in time?
Ah... At 2:00 PM.
And the return flight?
That... we'll book that only
after tomorrow's recording.
Deepu Chetta, the reason I didn't
enter the temple yesterday...
It's not something
anyone should be forced to do.
It's your choice.
God is inside us, after all.
Temples and churches
are just like mirrors
that reflect that power.
Dad's a bit upset...
that even after taking up pujas,
I still avoid entering temples.
I've already talked to him
and sorted it out.
Dad knows very well how
sincerely you perform the pujas.
And that's why
your pujas are so effective.
Exactly!
Hey...
- What is it?
- Huh?
- What?
- Don't you hear a sound...
coming from the car?
- Really?
- Yes.
Oh, yeah.
You've got such sharp ears, Indu!
Looks like the car is due
for a service.
Yes, yes.
17-B
You can sit here, Prabha.
I'll be over there.
I was in Bangalore.
Yes. I was in Bangalore.
Did you board the wrong flight?
This flight is going to Mumbai.
Prabha! It's me, Delulu!
Huh?
But how? You've started
possessing people now?
How else can I talk to you?
This girl was a perfect fit.
Hmm! Your 'perfection'
is getting out of hand!
Yes, yes.
Prabha, listen.
I used to fly from Kochi
airport to Bangalore.
I'm very sure.
Did getting on the flight
trigger her memories?
Quick! Remember the rest.
Who was the one who said "Yes"?
Think quickly!
Even half of it is fine.
We'll figure out the rest
on the return flight.
Don't stress yourself.
Perhaps it will just come back
bit by bit.
Prabha...
I'm sensing something else too.
What is it?
Now that I've remembered
this one thing,
I feel much lighter.
It feels like a burden
has been taken off me.
That's a good thing, right?
Guess you're on your way
to salvation.
I think once you find out
who said that 'Yes,'
you'll move on for good.
Full free!
So you won't miss me if I go?
Ha, great!
Isn't it more important
that you get your freedom?
Salvation is important!
Wow!
So you won't miss me at all, huh?
Psst!
Yeah?
I'll miss you too.
What?!
I will miss you.
Psst! Prabha!
Sorry! I lost the connection.
Sorry, Madam.
- Creep!
- Yup!
I knew you'd miss me!
[mocking] I knew you'd miss me!
Hello?
No.
He's almost here.
I've packed all his things
in carton boxes.
His clothes, shoes, and books.
And the bluetooth
speaker he gifted me.
Hey, he's here.
I'll call you later.
Thanks, dear.
Hey...
Are you okay, Saadhya?
I'll be fine.
Don't worry.
These are your things.
Thanks.
- See, I--
- I'm getting late for work.
You take care, okay?
Enjoy New York.
Superb!
Didn't I tell you?
He is such a find, Saadhya!
Prabhendu, beautiful!
Please come here.
Thank you, sir.
She is the one who found you.
- Oh.
- Hi.
Saadhya.
Faizal keeps talking about you.
He's your biggest
well-wisher, Prabhendu.
- Oh!
- Shift to Mumbai soon.
We need you here.
Sure, sir.
- Just a minute, Saadhya.
- Ah, sure, sir.
- Come on.
- Okay.
Good night, Prabhendu.
Until next time.
See you, sir.
See you.
I'm officially your fan, Prabha!
How do you play so well?
Well, that's just how talented I am!
Ugh!
Rupa has scheduled a puja
for tomorrow evening!
What do we do?
I've sent you the door password
for the service apartment.
The location too.
- It's close by.
- Got it.
Are you okay with the
evening flight tomorrow?
Err... is it possible to get a flight
that lands before noon tomorrow?
Ah... there's one at 6:30 AM.
Will that do?
I'm on that flight too.
Yeah, that's fine.
Okay.
Yes, it's okay.
You had dinner?
No.
Come on.
You can leave your bag here.
Okay.
Let's go.
We need to leave
for the airport at 4:30 AM.
- Okay.
- It'll be busy since it's the morning.
I brought my bags, thinking the
recording would go on all night.
You're amazing, Prabhendu!
You finished it so fast!
Pretty cool breeze, huh?
[mimicking Nivin Pauly]
Sorry.
She seems to be in
some kind of trouble.
I'll check.
Ugh! Classic heartbreak!
- Poor thing!
- Oh.
Aren't you eating?
Huh?
I asked...
aren't you eating?
Her boyfriend dumped her, Prabha.
Commitment issues.
Stop it, Delulu!
Poor girl. Still, she's handling
the situation so maturely.
Yeah.
Prabha, just ask her
if she's fine, no?
Uh... uh... uh...
What uh, uh, uh?
Don't just keep staring!
Say something!
Saadhya...
Aren't you eating
the bun and gravy?
Pav Bhaji.
Ah, Pav Bhaji.
Even though
I'm really angry with him...
he is actually a good guy.
My first instinct was to block him,
just like anyone would.
But then, I decided to
go through with it,
even though
it's a painful process.
It's better for getting
a proper closure.
Sometimes,
we can only blame the situation,
not the person.
If someone walks out of your life,
it's important to keep
your heart clear.
No anger, no grudges...
wishing only the best for them.
It's not easy.
But...
we get healed
just by being nice to them.
Prabha...
Are you able to see me?
Yeah.
I think I was in love.
I was in love with someone.
Do you remember his name?
So...
could he be the one
who said 'Yes'?
Then I should've been happy, right?
I didn't have to die!
Hello, sir.
Your friend has upgraded
you to an XL seat.
You can shift there
and sit more comfortably.
Thank you, sir.
Come.
Go on.
Won't this run?
It ran out of charge.
Uncle, you must've received an OTP.
Who are you calling "Uncle"?
Oh... sorry, bro.
An OTP must have come.
Could you tell me?
I've been sitting here for an hour.
I haven't seen anyone.
Prabhendu N. Namboothiri?
- Don't you have his number?
- I do.
Then just call and ask him.
Okay.
I thought you didn't believe
in ghosts and stuff.
- I don't believe in them, but I'm scared.
- Oh!
Aren't your mantras strong, sir?
Absolutely! A mantra saves
the one who chants it.
What was that line, Indu?
- A lie?
- Not a lie! A line!
Ah, it's
"Manana thraayathe ithi mantrah"
A doll!
Take the sacred ash.
Clean.
Let's go, let's go.
Wait, there's a guest room too.
- That's not really necess--
- Come on!
Clean!
Can we go now?
Close the window, Sashiyetta.
We don't want pigeons getting in.
Sir, next is the grandmother's room.
That's the main one.
You're not scared?
Of what?
You know plenty of mantras, right?
Chant them.
[chanting]
Come.
You too.
Who is he talking to?!
This is the grandmother's room.
After what happened,
not even the staff will enter here.
- She'd be in here all the time.
- Even now?
No, I mean before she died.
Okay.
She hardly slept.
Why are you telling me all this?
She really loved the balcony.
Why? Was she a smoker?
No, no.
To enjoy the breeze.
Shall we cleanse that area too?
Yeah! The balcony's safe.
There will be sunlight.
Open it! Open it!
Prabha!
What is it?
There...
Where?
- It's...
- What?
What?
What is it?
Don't kill us, sir!
We're not thieves, sir.
We were staying here
since it's an empty room.
- What?
- Is this the grandma?
Get out, you!
[panicked muttering]
Oh no!
Don't call the police, Chetta!
Is the spirit gone?
Yes!
Clean!
[indistinct chatter]
Hey, did you decide to stop doing pujas
because of what happened today?
Not all all!
Today's puja worked, right?
We got rid of the spirit,
didn't we?
It's just that...
The thought of you not
being here with me anymore…
I'll be in Bombay from next week...
busy with stage shows
and practice sessions.
I can't commit to pujas
in the middle of all that.
It'll be a hassle for you too.
Hey!
Just leave the sacred
thread on for now.
Drop by when you're free.
I don't feel as scared
when you're with me.
Here, take this.
It's 50K.
50K? Wasn't our deal 60-40?
You take the whole thing.
Consider it your
provident fund!
Also, if you get any puja work
in Bombay, don't say no.
I've never been on a flight.
Get up! Let's go!
What?
Huh!
Hmm?
What?
- Oh no!
- What is it?
- Snake?
- A snake?
Get inside!
It's not safe, not safe!
Let's go.
Wow! Such a brave ghost!
One, two...
Three and four...
Guys, guys, guys!
I have to give the final count
for food tomorrow.
- Is anyone else coming?
- Yes.
There's one more person.
Veg.
Hi, Prabhendu...
Shall I book our tickets to Bombay
together for next week?
With you on the flight,
I barely noticed we'd reached Kochi.
Thanks for the company.
There's one more.
Play, play, play!
Tomorrow evening is my
cousin's pre-wedding party.
Just reminding you, since you said
you might come if you're free.
I've sent the location.
What? Pookie Prabha
is feeling shy?
Why don't we go?
No, no, no.
You've got to play a little hard
to get, to be taken seriously.
Ugh!
When someone's being this frank,
don't put on
these stupid airs, okay?
I'm not putting on airs, Delulu.
I just feel weird when someone
gets close to me too quickly.
See… she just met us…
No, actually… sorry… met you.
Did she really have to tell you
her whole break-up story right away?
No.
I think she's into you.
No! It's…
Maybe it's just because
she cried in front of us.
Not just that!
Any other guy would have
used this chance to make a move.
And... don't think I'm saying this
to flatter you. But...
I think you are actually a nice guy.
Really?
Yeah!
In that case,
if I ask you something...
will you tell me the truth?
This is such a classic guy move!
When you're circling around for parking
and spot someone leaving a good space,
you just swoop straight in!
Love-sick fools!
Love?
And me?
Music is my only love!
Oh, spare me the drama!
Just leave music out of this.
And it's always the single guys
who are the most romantic!
Ugh!
What do you mean, "Ugh"?
Come here, Prabha.
Come here.
Sit down.
Prabha, a good relationship
just makes life better.
See... Someone who can understand
what's in your mind with a single glance...
And someone who can understand
the meaning of your silences.
Wouldn't it be great
to have that kind of support?
You're absolutely hell-bent on
making me park there, aren't you?
- Look, afterwards--
- That's not it.
Look, you'll be seeing
her again anyway.
So you'll have a good
friend in Mumbai.
We should go, Prabha.
It will be fun.
That place is on the outskirts.
Going by bike could be risky.
Why don't you take your dad's car?
Nah, that's not a good idea.
Why so much ego, Prabha?
It's not ego.
It's just--
Is that Pappu?
Yes.
How did he get in?
No idea.
All done, Pappu.
If we don't let this wound heal,
the doctor will have to operate
on you again, just like last time.
Sleep now, okay?
Just call me
if you need anything.
Dad is right here, okay?
You haven't slept?
No.
Pappu has a wound on him.
If he remains outside,
flies will land on the wound,
and it'll end up getting infected.
I feel at peace
when he's in here.
When did you start this?
Two years ago.
It used to be a big cylinder.
Deepu brought this one.
It's comfortable.
Please put that spray bottle
in the cupboard.
Pappu might chew on it.
I haven't moved
any of your mom's belongings.
Thulasi washes them every week.
I press them
and put them back.
When I open that cupboard,
I feel like Sujatha is here,
even if just for a little while.
It gives me strength.
You can go to bed, Indu.
We are okay.
Dad...
Can I...
take our car tomorrow?
"I saw you on the floor
In the crowd but alone"
"The music in my heart
Rings the lub-dub tone"
"Would you let me
sing my love?"
"I drifted through the night
You're the star in my sight"
"The beat makes it right
For me and you"
"Would you let me
sing my love?"
"My heartbeat feels true
Oh baby, looking at you"
"The music slows down
My sweetheart, dancing with you"
"As the new groom
arrives in splendid array"
"The whole place suddenly
glows in a lovely way"
"Like an ocean where
foaming waves lift and play"
"In this canopy decked
with garlands and bells"
"The colours now blossom
as beauty swells"
"Never to separate again"
"They must flow
through life's terrain"
"With one shared mind under the sun,
together… forever… as one"
"Smile and step where rhythms deploy,
ankle bells chiming in light convoy"
"O sparrows looping
in ecstatic ploy"
"Who is ready to dissolve
in that whirling joy?"
"In eyes lit bright where feelings beam,
there flickers softly a tender gleam"
"There's a tiny rattle
of naughty dreams that tattle"
"Yet no words can capture
such a dream"
"Without saying anything
to each other aloud"
"Through the sharpness of glances
their hearts have avowed"
"Will not all that's written
on life's turning page"
"Blossom forth as moonlight
that will never age?"
"Won't even their silence,
like a drifting cloud"
"Melt into honeyed words,
soft-falling, unbowed?"
"The umbrella is unfurling,
its shelter well dealt"
"And beneath its shade,
a calm is felt"
"Weaving a love as vast
as the ocean we span"
"Won't you and I rise
together like dawn…"
"Forever… as one?"
"I saw you on the floor
In the crowd but alone"
"The music in my heart
Rings the lub-dub tone"
"Would you let me
sing my love?"
"In eyes lit bright where feelings beam,
there flickers softly a tender gleam"
"There's a tiny rattle
of naughty dreams that tattle"
"Yet no words can capture
such a dream"
I need to tell you something, Prabha.
What is it?
I like you, Prabha.
Well...
I like you too, Delulu.
That's not what I meant.
I'm in love with you.
Thank you.
I love you too.
When I am speaking so frankly
without any ego,
why are you behaving like this?
When someone else showed up suddenly,
did I become nothing to you?
What's gotten into you, Delulu?
Weren't you the one who told me
to go meet Saadhya?
You're the one who set us up,
even after I said no.
Where did this love come from
all of a sudden,
like flipping a switch?
I don't know.
I don't know!
I can't hide things from the people
I care about the most.
I won't have any peace of mind.
And you're the only one I have!
I have no one else.
This is...
This is just a kind
of possessiveness.
You'll get over it.
Also,
even though you're a ghost,
you're not old enough
to get married.
And I'm almost past that age.
Prabha, stop calling me a "ghost"!
I've told you this many times.
Then what should I call you?
You don't know your name.
I can't even touch--
Prabha, love is not physical!
People love each other
from great distances.
People fall in love
even when they're much older.
It's about the deep
emotional connect we share.
We have that between us.
Can you honestly say
we don't have that?
That's not what I meant.
See...
I'm trying to be practical here.
When Saadhya hugged me today,
I felt my heart fill up.
It's the first time I've ever felt
something like that.
Today was the happiest
day of my life.
And you were the first person
I shared it with.
And now you've spoiled it!
You're so selfish!
You've changed so much, Prabha!
Your life has only gotten better
since I showed up, right?
I'm the reason
you even met Saadhya!
You are all the same!
All men are the same!
Answer the call.
I'm sorry.
Talk to her.
I need some privacy!
I'm the one who needs
salvation from you!
What the hell, man?
Don't you have anything
better to do, you jerk?
Annie...
Our daughter has something to tell you.
I know what it is.
Not happening, Vinod.
Huh!
She wants a new iPhone, right?
She's making a habit of this.
No, Mom.
It's not about an iPhone!
- Then what?
- It's... well...
Papa, just tell her!
Mummy...
Chechi wants to
dye her hair blue.
Not blue, Chacko!
Lavender!
- Oh, so I have to say that too?
- Ugh!
Oh, Papa, just tell her
the main matter now!
What is it?
Well, Annie...
We're not just their parents.
We're their best friends too, right?
Skip the intro.
Get to the point.
Our daughter likes someone.
Oh, it's that Joe from
Kottayam, isn't it?
The moment I saw his gaze,
I knew it.
Eww! Joe and Aishu are already
in a relationship.
Huh! Since when?
Papa!
Okay. Straight to the point.
It's someone she met in Bangalore.
Not from college,
but through a mutual friend.
I warned you before,
many guys will come after you,
so watch out.
Annie, let me complete.
She's the one
who's going to propose!
Yes.
See, we're the first ones
she's telling this to.
I think we should appreciate that.
Yeah, we should.
He's coming tomorrow.
We'll just meet him, grab a coffee,
and head back.
That's it.
Does he like you?
He hasn't said so yet...
But I'm so sure... we have
a deep emotional connect.
Show me his photo.
See, Papa?
What did I say?
This is the problem with Mummy.
She judges instantly by looks!
Ha! We're meeting him tomorrow,
aren't we, Annie?
What's the harm in
showing a picture?
You don't like beards, Mummy.
He has a beard.
Also...
He is a Hindu.
And he's a little older than me.
Jesus!
Hey, relax!
Her prediction is that you'll be
the first one to like him, Annie!
Let us go, Mummy.
Chechi will be happy.
- "Us"? No way!
- Huh?
You've got school tomorrow morning!
Your Papa and I
will meet him first.
- Yeah! Yaay!!
- Success!
I'll show you, okay?
I'm sure you'll be happy.
Promise?
Promise.
You know Varkey, right?
He runs the coffee shop here.
His cold coffee is
already famous, Annie.
Where is he?
He's late.
He needs time to get here, Mummy.
What is it?
Dear...
Papa, one sec.
He's not coming, right?
Yeah, he's not coming.
Are you happy now, Mummy?
Sorry, Papa.
I think he guessed it.
He guessed
why I asked him to come.
That's okay, dear.
It's alright.
We shouldn't expect anything
from anyone.
Your generation generally has a hesitation
to become committed.
It's quite natural, dear.
How can you judge someone
you don't even know, Mummy?
Papa, I think he is just confused.
Maybe it'll be fine
if I just talk to him.
Dear!
Rakhi, please ask the Head Boy
to come to my office.
Good afternoon, Ma'am.
Good afternoon.
Jacob V. Manjooran from 8-C...
His sister had an accident.
She's in critical condition.
Avinash, I need you to go with him
to the hospital.
I'll have a staff member
go with you.
- Okay, Ma'am.
- Jacob's parents will be there.
Till then, make sure that he's fine.
Sure, Ma'am.
She's in the ICU.
Third floor.
Papa...
Where is Chechi?
Chacko...
Do you know when your sister
was her happiest?
When you were born,
on the floor right below us.
To make your Chechi happy now,
Papa needs your help
with something.
The doctors are saying...
that your sister is gone.
Her brain is dead.
To stop the machine support...
and set her free...
they need my permission.
They need a... "Yes" from me.
But...
unless... unless you also say "Yes"...
I won't say "Yes."
If I say "Yes"...
will Chechi be happy?
Yes.
Promise?
Promise.
Yes!
My Papa's name is
Vinod Mathew Manjooran.
We have a plantation.
Magic Hills Plantation.
It's in Kuttikkanam.
My Mummy's name is Annie.
Chacko's real name is Jacob.
Same name as my grandfather.
What's your name?
Delulu.
That's just the name
we gave you, right?
What's your real name?
Delulu...
means delusion...
means Maya.
Maya Mathew.
"Don't leave; don't make my eyes
turn to tears"
"Don't disappear and fill my heart
with painful spears"
"Wasn't it in your eyes
that I saw myself clearer"
"As though I stood
before a living mirror?"
"When I stood all alone
in silent plea"
"Didn't you arrive
and breathe life into me?"
"As I climbed the steps
where darkness spread"
"To sparkle and shine
in the path ahead"
"You appeared as a star in golden frame,
you rose as a lamp with a steady flame"
"You flew from the sky
and landed with art"
"Resting gently
on the branch of my heart"
"O petal, O angel,
sweet counterpart"
"O magic unending,
eternally rare"
"May you never
disappear anywhere"
"O magic unending,
eternally rare"
"May you never
disappear anywhere"
"Don't leave; don't make my eyes
turn to tears"
"Don't disappear and fill my heart
with painful spears"
"The memories simply soak
in the rain of sorrow's tears"
"And in that rain your face appears,
whispering its stories to my ears"
"The summer of separation
scorches everything in sight"
"And in that heat, thoughts of you
smoulder like an ember bright"
"O smile that enfolds me
in wings of feathered gleam"
"Do not fade like an unseen wind
lost in a dream"
"You flew from the sky
and landed with art"
"Resting gently
on the branch of my heart"
"O petal, O angel,
sweet counterpart"
"O magic unending,
eternally rare"
"May you never
disappear anywhere"
"O magic unending,
eternally rare"
"May you never
disappear anywhere"
Indu...
Everything you said
could be your imagination,
or it could be true.
I'd like to believe
that it's true.
Her parents haven't seen
the person she loved, till date.
A soul can find
peace and salvation
only by freeing itself
from sorrow!
Lakshmy, the guest room first.
Okay, Madam.
- Would this do?
- Yes.
Yes?
I'm a friend of Maya's.
I was in the area
and thought I'd drop by.
Oh.
Come in.
Maya always used to say...
that regardless of how much
you both fought,
when she was away,
the one she missed the most...
was her mom.
She's a big liar.
She'd say the exact same thing
about her Papa.
We still haven't been able
to accept that reality
So, we don't really...
miss her, as such.
Her Papa has turned
into a complete workaholic.
And Chacko keeps studying
all the time.
He's even the class topper now.
But there are two things
that really trouble me.
I miss her whenever I open
the fridge in the kitchen.
She always used to walk over
and open the fridge,
ever since she was a little girl.
And then, when I see clothes
lying all over the bed.
No matter how many times I told her,
she always left her clothes on the bed.
Clothes were her weakness.
She was always on her phone,
browsing for them.
Let me get you
something to drink.
"You don't like beards, Mummy."
"He has a beard."
"And..."
"He is a Hindu."
"And he's a little older than me."
What's your name?
Prabhendu.
You were the one she was in love with...
Isn't that right, Prabhendu?
Yes.
"When someone sat close to me at night,
like new-fallen rain in cool delight"
"My heart shifted, lighter than ever,
turning at once to a moonlit river"
"Slowly unfolding its wings
in tender delight"
"Weaving a chain of laughter
pure and bright"
"My mind fills up
on its own tonight"
"Come, let's go to distances
we've never seen"
"Becoming two lovely,
colourful clouds serene"
"In this new birth
where our paths convene"
"Let's find our shelter on a blossom
branch kissed by morning dew"
"Becoming the breath
that rises soft and true"
"Till every painful memory
softens and bids adieu"