and is meant solely for
the purpose of entertainment.
All characters, events, locations, institutions,
and communities, etc. are entirely fictitious.
'Bear no resemblance
to anyone, living or dead' Show less
[Vintage Malayalam song playing]
[Musical Night
by Cochin Kalamela]
- Hey, son... Psst!
- Huh?
Here's the orchestra list.
This is the final song.
Don't forget to add my name
at the end of the announcement.
Saji Pattambi, Troupe Manager.
Got it?
- What was that?
- Saji Pattambi!
- Right, right.
- Okay.
[song continues]
- Hey, Razak...
- Yeah?
The visas for the Europe trip arrived.
Good for you, Saji Chetta.
Oh no!
What's wrong?
We submitted 15 passports
for the trip.
But we got visas
for only 14 people.
One person's visa is missing.
Whose visa is it?
Keyboard: Francis.
Francis Chettan is cleared.
Violin: Xavier,
Linto,
Kundara Das.
The entire violin team
has received visas.
Tumba: Joy.
Tumba Joy made it too.
Tabla: Surendran, Chacko.
Even Chacko, the troublemaker,
got through.
Prabhendu on electric guitar.
- Hey, Razak...
- Yeah?
It's Prabhendu who didn't
get the visa.
- And then?
- Huh?!
Okay, okay.
Let me sleep for a bit.
Prabha...
What's going on?
I'm searching for a jacket
to handle the cold in Europe.
My jacket from the US tour
has turned all mouldy.
I have to place the order today
to get it before we leave.
Ah, true, true.
Hey, that room behind
our rehearsal space...
I'm going to use it
for two months, okay?
I'm vacating my current apartment.
So, to store my stuff...
So you already vacated your flat?
What is this? You could've
at least asked me first!
Just a second.
Let me just enter this OTP.
- Wait, wait! Don't enter it!
- 4--
They've cut the electric guitar, man.
You're the only one
who's not coming on the trip!
What?!
And then?
- Who's having the omelette?
- Just keep it here.
How about some
chicken fry for you, sir?
It's our speciality.
We've also got quail fry.
- No need.
- We have pork with Chinese potatoes.
- It's amazing.
- Get going, will you?
He's a Namboothiri (Brahmin).
Pure veg.
Then I'll remove the pork
and get him the Chinese potatoes.
Hey, this isn't some wedding spread
where food keeps coming.
I still have to pay you, right?
Will this idiot go around
asking everyone the same thing?
We don't even have enough budget
for everyone's omelettes.
If budget was a problem,
you should've said it earlier.
You know, adding an omelette to
the dosa gives it a touch of luxury.
I mean the electric guitar here,
not the omelette!
Yeah, I asked them
the exact same thing.
Then, that sponsor guy
sent a message.
Let me find it.
Chetta, one of the investors
pulled out at the last minute.
We can pull through only
if we remove one person.
- So I...
- And also...
Please convey my special apologies
to Prabhendu Ma'am.
Prabhendu "Ma'am"?
Idiot!
Look, Prabha...
Don't think I'm just trying
to make you feel better.
What if this is actually
for the best?
What? Being broke,
homeless for two months, and starving?!
Oh, give me a break!
It's not like you come from
some poor household!
Wouldn't even a tiny bit of
your dad's and brother's puja income
be enough for you
to manage a full Europe tour?
Wasn't it your ego that made you
snap your sacred thread
and choose to live by cutting costs?
If someone loses faith
and becomes an atheist,
that's their personal choice.
That is not ego.
That's confidence.
- No, Prabha... I didn't mean--
- I'm not finished.
To become a truly
passionate musician,
you have to sacrifice
a lot of things.
Just imagine if A.R. Rahman
had played it safe,
packed his lunch every day
and gone to a bank job,
would we have even half the songs
we performed on stage today?
Prabha, I wasn't trying
to argue with you.
What I actually wanted to talk about
was the passion you have.
You're the most talented person
in our troupe.
Have any of these guys
ever played for a movie?
You're the only one they call
for studio recordings, right?
But that only happens
once in a while, right?
Anyway, since your trip is cancelled,
you should attend your father's
70th birthday celebration.
Your elder brother called you
so many times, right?
No, that's not a good idea.
Look...
There's a proven trend of grumpy dads
becoming warm and loving
once they hit 70.
This is your chance to slip in
and stay there for some time.
You can save money
on food and rent, right?
Plus, free WiFi, free laundry!
How great is that?
Hey, son!
Got any quail eggs?
Him and his damn eggs!
Eggs! Eggs! Eggs!
Where do you keep
shoving all these eggs?
So now it's quail eggs
instead of chicken eggs?
Can't you eat a meal
without eggs, huh?
[Radiant at 70
- Neelakandan Namboothiri]
Indu...
I know you won't come.
But still, whenever you're
free, if you come home,
it would make Dad very happy,
even if he doesn't express it.
Even uncle keeps talking
about wanting to see you.
I'm busy.
I'll try.
Passengers getting down at this stop,
please step out.
[Radiant at 70
- Neelakandan Namboothiri]
Hello...
Huh?
Aadi, no.
You'll get hurt.
When was this?
What?
What did you see while passing?
You must stay for lunch, okay?
There's nothing wrong with Dad.
Just stop the car
and read that flex board properly.
Flex boards aren't
just for funerals, you know!
Okay.
What is it, Thulasi?
Your Dad had asked me to let him know
once the water filter service is done.
Ask them to wait for a bit.
I'll tell Dad right after
the Minister leaves.
This is my eldest son, Deepankuran.
He was with me at Sabarimala.
Then I must have seen him.
Do you work with your Dad
at the temple here?
Oh no.
He's always abroad.
He handles only VIP pujas.
He's flying to Kenya tonight.
And from there, to Dubai.
He even moved closer
to the airport for convenience.
And this is his wife.
Where is your younger son?
He'll be late.
- Let's click the photo.
- Alright.
Sir, over here!
Hey, Pappu!
Why are you coming in
from the back, Indu?
There were too many people
at the front, Thulasi Chechi.
Dad was there too.
I just wanted to avoid
creating a scene.
And this way,
I could see Pappu too.
Not Pappu.
You have to call him "Uncle Pappu" now.
When your mother brought him here
from behind the temple,
my child
was only four days old then.
She's studying in fifth grade now.
He really lost all his cheer
after Mom passed away, didn't he?
Not just him…
You did too.
[Sanskrit news plays on radio]
Sigh! How many times do I have to tell him?
Ugh!
Welcome back, Indu!
You know, if you press that
like this after peeing, it sprays water.
It doesn't even take a second.
Why do you have to make
the whole room stink?
We're already peeing
into water, aren't we?
So why flush more water in?
Aha! So uncle's favourite is here!
Indu, I need to leave right away
to catch my flight.
Go take a quick shower,
wear a nice mundu,
and go take care
of things downstairs.
I have a doubt, Uncle.
For the puja in Kenya, ebony twigs
are required for the sacred fire.
That's not easy
to get at the moment.
And we also need
to check in early.
Is there an alternative I can use?
- Isn't it for an auspicious occasion?
- Yes.
Then just use small twigs
from the Bael tree.
That's a relief!
We have Bael in stock.
Okay, so that's sorted.
Want me to bring you anything
from Kenya?
Bring back a Kenyan beauty
for our chronic bachelor here.
Sounds good. Just make sure
she belongs to the Namboothiri clan!
Yeah, right!
High hopes you have!
- Okay. I'll call you, Indu.
- Okay.
- I'll come see you when I'm back.
- Alright, alright.
Deepu Chettan bought
his assistant a car.
I heard he pays him very well, too.
If you still had your sacred thread on,
Deepu would've taken you along.
Had you stayed with Neelakandan,
you would've been the chief priest
of our family temple by now.
Well, it's all because
of the path you chose, isn't it?
At least what I chose...
is something I can feel and hear.
All you have is hype, right?
There's nothing to see or hear.
That's enough.
He's just ignorant!
Forgive this ignorant fool,
O Lord!
And please remind him to flush
after he urinates, O Lord!
Please don't mind!
[Chanting mantras]
Rupesh, the owner of the
shop is this madam here.
Oh!
I'm not saying this just because I did it,
but the puja was a big success.
It's all the Lord's blessing.
Correct.
- Sreekutta...
- Yes.
Hare Krishna, Hare Krishna,
Krishna Krishna Hare Hare.
Hmm!
Hare Rama, Hare Rama,
Rama Rama Hare Hare.
Hare Krishna, Hare Krishna,
Krishna Krishna Hare Hare.
Hare Rama, Hare Rama,
Rama Rama Hare Hare.
Hare Krishna, Hare Krishna...
Sreekutta...
You can take it yourself, sir.
I'm not saying this
just because I did it,
but the puja was a big success.
- So?
- So, well...
- Sreekutta...
- Yes.
Just check whether
that broom works.
The broom is in
excellent working condition.
But you'll need to pay me extra
for cleaning.
Don't be so greedy, Sreekutta.
Why shouldn't I be?
Don't I take on
these low-budget pujas for you too?
- Is that so?
- Yes.
Then why were you trying to find
a new assistant instead of me?
No way!
Would I ever do that?
Oh, really?
Just a minute.
Bhasi, that Sreekuttan
is a complete fraud.
Do you know anyone else
who can assist me?
Even if I say all this,
I'm really fond of you.
Of course, I know that,
Rupeshetta!
And that ₹500
the madam gave…
I'm keeping it.
Just consider it
my travel expense.
- Huh?
- Yeah.
- Aren't you happy, Rupeshetta?
- Yes.
I'll get going.
I've got work.
- Pavithran...
- Yes?
We need to leave at
4:30 AM tomorrow.
Okay.
Unni, start cutting vegetables
for the Sambar at 3:30 AM.
So where's the feast, Aunty?
In Thrissur.
Oh! You got your bike fixed?
That's great.
- I'll be here for a couple of months.
- Okay.
The 70th birthday feast
was fantastic, Uncle.
I couldn't eat on a banana leaf
because I arrived late.
Come on! Subramanyan Namboothiri's
feast must be eaten on a banana leaf!
It's really embarrassing when you talk
about yourself in the third person, Dad!
Hello!
Give me your phone, Mom.
How's your uncle keeping, Indu?
He's doing well overall.
Only his leg is giving him some trouble.
Hey, do you need a towel?
No need. I showered
before I came.
- I'm heading to the temple pond.
- Okay.
Looking handsome!
What's on Aunty's mobile phone?
I just checked Anagha's WhatsApp status.
I can't see it.
She blocked me
after we broke up.
- Aren't you ashamed?
- Why should I be?
It's not like I'm bothering her.
Even if we're out
in the semi-finals,
we still need to know
who wins the cup, right?
And don't step on the snake.
- What?
Ugh! Aren't you ashamed?
- Rupe...
- Yeah?
Do you know of any jobs
that could help me get by
for the next couple of months?
There are many options
in my dad's line of work.
Would you be willing
to serve at feasts?
No, that won't suit me.
Too many people, too much noise…
Do you know
how to grate coconuts?
How about chopping vegetables?
No way! If I hurt my hand,
I won't be able to play the guitar.
Why don't you just
work as my assistant?
As a priest's assistant?
That's not happening.
Didn't you and your brother Deepu
study the Vedas properly together?
Even after all this time,
I haven't learned as much as you.
But I'm still able
to keep it going, right?
But that was ages ago.
I'm not really convinced about
this whole "God" concept anymore.
In that case, are you certain
we'll even be alive tomorrow?
That just comes down to luck.
So why not treat
that luck as God?
Hey, tell them to buy it
only if they really need it!
[in Hindi] Take it, Bhai.
You'll have fun.
[in Hindi]
Bhai, this is quality stuff.
Hey, where are
those guys headed?
This has been going on
for a week.
No fire, no smoke.
Must be hard-core stuff!
Here? With me around?
How dare they!
- Rupe...
- I'm not the same Rupa anymore. Move!
Rupe, drop it!
You'll land in trouble!
This is common everywhere!
Just zip it!
Hey! Hey!
Who are you guys? Huh?
What's going on here?
Go on! Go home!
Clear out!
Want me to call the cops?
[In Hindi]
Go, go! Go home!
Say something, man.
Who the hell are you guys?
Look at those jeans,
that bag, that chain!
You better cut that hair
and beard tomorrow!
Just chase this pest away.
Scared?
Me? What for?
Oh no!
No, child!
Don't do that!
I said don't!
Oh, Goddess!
Don't! Oh, Goddess!
- Run!
- I am running!
That child has such perfect aim!
Indu, I am coming!
Take the soap and towel with you.
Okay.
Chetta, that was awesome!
You elevated the song
to the next level.
It's all because of
the Goddess's grace!
- Right, chetta?
- Yes, yes.
Can I just GPay you?
You don't have cash?
Err... Sanaletta...
We don't have cash.
It'll be credited to your account.
Don't worry.
Nice work.
Psst... Psst!
I've told you so many times
not to call me for these
low-budget music albums.
Oh, I see!
You said I should call you
even for a ₹1000 job.
This one pays ₹2500.
- Then where is it?
- It'll come when it comes.
I barely have money
to get home, Faizal.
Don't get stressed, Prabha.
Money comes today,
goes tomorrow.
How can it go tomorrow
if it hasn't come today?!
You know the composer
Viraj Trivedi, right?
He's looking for new
electric guitarists from Kerala.
There's a new Malayali girl
in his management team.
That's where this came from.
Remember the session
you did for Justin?
I've already sent it to them!
All his movie and stage-show teams
are from Mumbai.
Photo! Photo!
But it's worth a shot, right?
- What?
- I said, we can try!
Okay.
Is this to check your oxygen level?
It's for credit card verification.
- Want one?
- No, no! It's too stressful!
You can withdraw up to
₹60,000 per month, sir.
- Really?
- Yes.
Hell yeah!
Bro, get him one.
What do you do for a living, sir?
I'm a musician.
Oh, then you'll definitely be rejected.
- Huh?!
- Sign here.
Sir, one photo.
Don't smile so much.
Bro!
You got ₹200?
I went to Ernakulam yesterday
and came back with nothing.
There's zero stock!
How would I have money?!
Why don't you just ask your dad?
Me? Ask him?
Not in this lifetime!
What is it?
Never mind, it's fine.
Who is fine? Me?
Well, not that...
If you have something to say,
just say it.
Do you have change?
How much for?
For... errr... two hundred.
Will two hundreds work?
A single 200 rupee note
is also fine.
Then that isn't really
'change,' is it?
Why do you need it?
Just to step out for a while.
Then why don't you just…
step out?
I was thinking
I'd get a tea as well.
Oh...
- One minute.
- Okay.
You recognise us, don't you?
Of course!
I remember seeing your daughter
when she was very young.
She's grown up so much!
Oh no, she's just my neighbour.
When I told her
we were coming here,
she came along
to see your ancestral house.
Yeah, yeah.
Oh, sorry!
You both have a son, right?
This is my brother.
My husband is in Qatar.
It's okay.
Don't worry.
Here you go.
There's enough tea
for three cups.
Help yourself
whenever you want.
Okay?
Back in our day, if Father knew
I drank tea from outside,
I'd get beaten instantly.
Kids these days...
they are just different.
That was funny!
Weren't you the first one
to gain fame here, Prahladan Namboothiri?
Even my father
started off as your assistant, right?
So what?
How do you put up with Dad's
attitude and still stay here?
Because I'm very fond of myself.
Huh?!
What do we really want in life?
Someone who loves us dearly,
and takes good care of us.
Right?
Yes.
Why can't I be that person?
I love myself dearly.
And I take very good care of myself.
You don't care about anyone but yourself!
You have no idea what
I'm going through!
[quotes a sloka from the Mahabharata]
What comes next?
Say it out loud.
Don't you know this sloka?
[completes the sloka]
What does it mean?
No crisis can take away
your ability to think.
If you apply that ability,
wealth can be earned again.
Simple.
That's it.
Now go on, earn.
Aunty, where's Rupesh?
He's bathing in our pond.
I don't know why...
He's stopped going to the temple pond.
Rupe...
Yeah?
I'm ready.
Ready for what?
I'm ready to put on
the sacred thread
and perform pujas.
"The crystal-clear star
in the heavens so bright"
"It's holding its solemn vigil
in worshipful light"
"To the tune of the soft chant
in gentle sway"
"That blooms on the tongue's tip
in a blossoming way"
"Within the realm of fading memories
that drift like shade"
"The Vedas endure,
refusing to fade"
"Counting them one by one
as patterns shift"
"Habits change,
letting the unwanted drift"
"Not seeing with the outer eyes,
perceiving where the inner soul lies"
"Without seeking the safety
of faith's embrace"
"On the stylus tip where thought arises,
what counts as truth, what slips as lies"
"Don't worry about any of that today,
Just turn to yourself, be yourself your way"
'Sarvam Maya'
[Everything is a Delusion]
"The crystal-clear star
in the heavens so bright"
"It's holding its solemn vigil
in worshipful light"
"To the tune of the soft chant
in gentle sway"
"That blooms on the tongue's tip
in a blossoming way"
"Within the realm of fading memories
that drift like shade"
"The Vedas endure,
refusing to fade"
"Counting them one by one
as patterns shift"
"Habits change,
letting the unwanted drift"
"In some distant sanctuary
set high in the sky"
"Who is there above us
to whom we must bow or comply?"
"Is any light greater,
any radiance akin"
"Than the fire that blazes brightly,
fiercely within?"
Seriously? Lighting a match
in a fireworks shop?
"This is the start,
the time to prepare with heart…"
"We must seize the battlefield,
whatever it costs"
"We must loosen the tangles,
undo all the knots…"
"We must chant the mantra fearlessly,
and must rise to our victory"
"Let us move forward,
ahead of the rest"
"By your own true being,
Blaze forth as lightning at its best"
"As time's own phases onward glide,
as your rituals flow in a faithful tide"
"As your deeds take form on life's broad shelf,
discover yourself within your self"
"The crystal-clear star
in the heavens so bright"
"It's holding its solemn vigil
in worshipful light"
"To the tune of the soft chant
in gentle sway"
"That blooms on the tongue's tip
in a blossoming way"
Run! Run! Catch him!
- Indu...
- Yeah?
I just noticed something.
Has your accent changed slightly?
- Is that what has come to pass?
- Yes!
Exactly!
That's our traditional accent.
Does that really matter?
Priest, breakfast is ready.
- Please have it before you leave.
- Is that so?
- Can't we just eat at home later?
- There's only Upma at home.
It's masala dosa here.
I'll be right back.
Oh dear...
Five, six...
6 x 5 = 36...
It's okay.
Move.
This looks good!
- Did you make this, Paulose?
- Yes.
- Is it made of teak?
Paulose insists it's teak.
Then it must've cost a lot.
Anything Paulose builds
never comes cheap, right?
I just hope it's sturdy enough.
It's sturdier than
the wig on your head.
Better hold on to it.
Don't let it fly away.
How many people can
sit on this, Paulose?
It won't move an inch
even if the whole village sits on it.
Stop exaggerating, Paulose!
Me? Exaggerating?
Please step aside, sir.
I'll prove it now!
All of you, move aside.
Come here, son.
You sit there.
All you kids,
go and sit.
Go sit, Chechi.
Go on.
Come on, everyone.
Come and sit.
- What? You want to sit, Priest?
- No, no.
Please sit.
It'll be an honour.
Move aside.
Let the priest sit.
- No, really...
- Go on, sit.
How about now?
Call your dad or mom,
whoever's around.
Let them try swinging on it.
Psst...
Coming?
Come here, big shot!
Give it a good push!
Oh my!
Oh no!
Nothing to worry!
The swing is perfectly fine.
Go on, cry again.
Shush!
Move, move!
Rupe!
Does it hurt, son?
Not at all.
The doctor said the MRI scan showed
nothing wrong with his head.
Such a waste of money!
At least the X-ray
was worth it.
It shows swelling at two spots
on his spine.
Luckily, with Indu around, all the
pujas you agreed to won't be cancelled.
- Yes.
- Hmm.
Now, if you both could step outside.
I need to talk to Indu in private.
Go on.
Go on, Mom!
Let's go.
Indu
- Indu...
- Yeah?
Yes, I'm your cousin.
But now...
Now what?
Now I'm your employer too.
So what?
You're fully capable
of doing pujas on your own now,
and making your own money.
That makes me proud.
Look, I'm not planning
to do this forever.
I'll leave once
I'm financially stable.
Sure, you can leave.
That's not my point.
From tomorrow, we split
whatever you earn from the pujas,
fifty-fifty.
Huh?!
But I'm the one
doing the puja!
And I'm the one
bringing in the clients, right?
- Rupe!
- Listen, Indu...
When family and friends
turn into business partners,
having clarity about financial matters
can help prevent future conflicts.
There's no point
spoiling our relationship over it.
That's all I wanted to say.
- 60-40.
- Yeah, that's fine. Fine.
40 is fine, 40 is fine.
You are happy, right?
"It clears up like the sky
in its vast renew"
"It fills like the ocean of milk
breaking through"
"Ascend the chariot of that wisdom
alive within you"
"And continue your journey,
steady and true"
"Every single battle
that comes our way"
"Let us face it with
blazing determination each day"
"On the stylus tip where thought arises,
what counts as truth, what slips as lies"
"Don't worry about any of that today,
Just turn to yourself, be yourself your way"
"The crystal-clear star
in the heavens so bright"
"It's holding its solemn vigil
in worshipful light"
"To the tune of the soft chant
in gentle sway"
"That blooms on the tongue's tip
in a blossoming way"
"Within the realm of fading memories
that drift like shade"
"The Vedas endure,
refusing to fade"
"Counting them one by one
as patterns shift"
"Habits change,
letting the unwanted drift"
Prabha...
Just a minute.
- Almost done.
- Okay.
Hey, Prabha...
Faizal told me.
Congrats!
Don't forget us
when you make it big in Bombay!
Oh, come on!
Hey...
I've sent you a
request on Instagram.
I'm not very active on it.
Well, you can just accept it
right now.
Oh... just a minute.
Hey, Rupe...
Indu, where are you?
Remember I told you about
Viraj Trivedi, the Hindi music director?
He loved the track
I sent him.
He has called me to the studio
for a video call session.
Wow, congrats!
That's amazing!
What are you doing
tomorrow evening?
I've got a Ganesha Puja
at Kadampuzha at dawn.
I thought I'd watch a movie
later in the evening.
Ugh! That's a horrible movie!
But I never told you
which movie it was!
Oh, you didn't?
- He didn't!
- Yeah, you didn't.
Anyway, listen...
Can you handle
one more puja tomorrow?
You can go after 6:00 PM.
The pay is huge!
The biggest one our astrologer
Krishnanunni has ever given us!
What kind of puja?
A lawyer from Palakkad...
His son who's a 12th grade student,
is said to be possessed.
He's been seeing and hearing things.
Rupe, I honestly don't know
anything about exorcisms.
Hey, I'll walk you through it.
I'll send you a PDF on WhatsApp
with updated chants and procedures.
Otherwise, it's the same
Sudarshana Homam setup.
Just add more fire and flowers
for extra punch.
Sometimes I wonder why we named
you 'Rupe'. You're obsessed with money.
How is that my fault?
Hey... please!
Alright.
- And hey, don't forget... 60-40.
Yeah, okay.
Hey Prabha...
Sorry, man. Not today.
Viraj sir's manager just called.
He worked through the night
and is sleeping during the day.
Okay.
That's fine.
Just keep me posted next time.
Okay?
Okay.
So...
Can you add my Insta ID now?
Chokichosky.
Chokay... I mean, okay.
[Straight from the heart]
If you're going for physiotherapy,
use the car.
Ha! It's such a struggle for me
to climb down into that low car
and then haul myself back up.
An auto rickshaw is far
more comfortable.
Don't you have a puja today?
Yes.
- Be careful.
- Okay.
What, am I supposed
to drive it myself now?
Hey, what's all this
you've been chopping off?
Will you destroy all the plants?
For the plants,
this is just like a haircut.
They might even
be enjoying it.
I'm crazy about plants, you know.
Shall we go?
Name?
Hibiscus rosa-sinensis.
It's also called "China Rose".
Not that!
What's your name?
Oh!
I'm Animon.
- Ready to go?
- Yeah, let's go.
Feel free to take the car
when you go for your pujas.
It's okay.
I'll just go in this auto.
What puja is happening
so late, sir?
Is it for the Goddess?
No! It's an exorcism.
- Advocate Dileep?
- Yes.
Rupesh had called.
Need a hand with your supplies?
No, it's fine.
I have someone with--
I'll call the driver.
Can I keep this here?
Yes, please.
Just the grass mat is left, right?
Yes, that's it.
- You can bring the boy in 10 minutes.
- Okay.
Deepthi Chechi!
Here you go.
It'll be ready in 10 minutes.
Alright.
Do you practice
at the District Court here?
Yes, for the past two months.
- I'm from Kuttikkanam.
- I see.
Whose guitar is that?
That's Kuttu's.
Ah... I mean, Avinash.
He plays really well.
He always says,
"I'm hungry, Latha Chechi."
Now, he has zero appetite.
Oh.
Didn't you take him
to a doctor?
We did. There's a doctor
at NIMHANS.
Dr. Raphael.
He's brilliant.
We consulted him.
Kuttu is on medication too.
But my wife insisted
on having this puja done.
I don't really believe in any of this.
You can sit.
Kutta... Sit down, son.
Sit down.
You can sit with him, Ma'am.
That will make him
more comfortable.
Sit down, son.
When did all this begin?
It's been about a week now.
One night, he walked into our room crying
and lay down beside us.
He says someone keeps approaching him,
trying to say something.
A man or a woman?
It's a young girl.
Now he needs me with him 24/7.
Even when he goes
to the bathroom!
Hello!
He makes no eye contact at all now.
I see.
We're about to begin the puja.
The spiritual reading suggests
this is a case of possession.
Once this puja is complete,
the spirit will leave his body
and merge with the supreme.
Hi Latha Chechi...
Huh?
Kuttu! Oh, my son!
Latha, are you seeing this?
It worked?
Dileepetta!
That's not possible!
- Look, our son!
- Hey, Kuttu! Are you okay?
Yeah, I am okay.
Deepthi!
See? Didn't I tell you?
[internalized sacred echoes]
- Gho...
Go on, say it.
You go ahead.
The ghost is definitely gone.
All the chants I sent you
worked like a charm.
Oh, come on! They had already
consulted a doctor.
I think the medicine
finally kicked in.
Oh...
Still, if that lawyer paid ₹1 lakh
instead of the ₹60,000 we asked…
- Indu...
- What?
Ever since you started wearing
the sacred thread and doing pujas,
don't you feel some
kind of divine presence?
I see this as
a job I'm paid for.
So shouldn't I just be sincere,
stay disciplined,
and do the job I was hired for
as honestly as I can?
- You should.
- That's what this 'presence' means to me.
Oh.
I'm leaving.
And I need a three-day break,
starting day after tomorrow.
Oh no, no, no!
I've already scheduled
three pujas for you!
- Take your break after that.
- No! No way!
How about 60-40?
- 70-30.
- Okay.
Mom, give me your phone.
She hasn't posted
any status update today!
Oh.
Hello?
There are several types of
silver idols here for today's ritual.
I've sent you the photos.
Which one should I get?
Oh, just a second.
Get the smallest one.
Okay, okay.
I'll take this one.
By the way, who's that Chinese fellow
in your WhatsApp DP?
Chinese fellow?
He's a Korean singer.
Oh, I see.
For a moment, I thought
I'd called the wrong person.
- Alright then.
- Okay.
Thank you.
Okay.
Hello.
You're Prabhendu, aren't you?
I'm Sreekuttan.
I used to be
Rupeshettan's assistant.
Oh!
Rupeshettan used
to talk about a cousin
who left home twelve years ago,
threw away his sacred thread, and has
been wandering around playing the guitar.
So that's you, huh?
And on top of that, you're an atheist!
Good heavens!
Let's keep this between us.
So what if I charge a little extra?
You're better off with me by your side.
Okay, right?
Yes, we're okay!
[indistinct chatter]
Oh dear...
Come on
What just happened?
He must be hurt.
Move, move.
[indistinct chatter]
- Are you hurt?
- You're okay, right?
- Hello!
- Is he okay?
Oh Goddess!
If I've done anything wrong
without meaning to,
please forgive me, Priest.
Let's go.
Chechi, are you Prabhendu?
- Huh?
- I asked if you're Prabhendu.
- No. Why?
- I have a parcel for Prabhendu.
- Give it to me.
- To you?
- What's the problem?
- Go call Prabhendu Chechi.
I'll hand it over to her myself.
Not Chechi.
He's a Chettan.
- Chettan?
- Yes.
Alright. Go call him then.
I'll make sure
the crows don't peck it.
Wait here.
There's a parcel for you, Indutty.
For me?
What could it be?
I haven't ordered anything!
Maybe you've got the wrong address.
Prabhendu N. Namboothiri,
Mullasseri House.
That's you, right?
- Yeah.
- Here you go.
But I don't even have your app
on my phone...
It's there, right?
You'll get an OTP.
Can you read it out?
- 6, 2, 0...
- 4, 0, 9.
- Okay.
- Wait, what about the payment?
That's already done.
Payment was through credit card.
Credit card?
But I never added my credit card to--
So that's saved too?
This is clearly a mistake.
Please return this.
I can't just take it back.
I need a return token
from the company.
That'll take a couple of days.
I swear, I didn't order this.
Sir, if you have a complaint,
take your time
and call customer care.
That's what they're there for, right?
What's going on with your phone?
You've been glued to it for a while.
I'm just deleting some unnecessary apps
from my phone, Uncle.
The WhatsApp photo keeps
changing on its own!
It's downloading apps on its own
and ordering clothes with my credit card!
Must be some Chinese app.
Did you lose any money?
Yup.
I've requested a refund.
Hopefully it comes through.
Hi!
Hey, don't panic.
I'll go and come back later.
Bye!
Why did you sleep here last night?
What's with this sudden affection?
I had a dream last night.
It really shook me.
Oh!
There was a girl...
She was just sitting there, staring at me.
A very beautiful girl.
That's a standard dream for bachelors
well past their marriage age.
Even at my age,
I get such dreams.
So naturally, you would too!
This wasn't like that.
I even heard her voice clearly.
She said,
"I'll go and come back later."
This is a 90-year-old
ancestral home, right?
All sorts of things can show up here.
Damn!
I've been available right next
door for all these years,
and not a single one
ever came to see me!
Nah, this one seems pretty modern.
She didn't even try to scare me.
She was just sitting there casually,
scrolling through my phone.
Next time you see her,
send her my way.
At least I'll have some company.
Hey, call Paul and ask him
to send an auto rickshaw.
I've got a meeting at ten.
Okay.
Hi!
Good morning.
Please, come in.
Come on in.
Kuttoos had an Android phone, you know.
I was never really
comfortable with Android.
The fact that you have an iPhone
is such a relief, Prabha!
Which 'Kuttoos'?
Remember the puja you did that day?
What was his real name again?
Oh... Avinash!
Gosh, he was such a cutie!
But scared out of his mind.
So scared,
he wouldn't even make eye contact!
How are you supposed to talk to someone
who won't even look at you?
But you're very brave, Prabha.
You have good eye contact.
I like it.
Ten on Ten!
But you did get scared yesterday.
It's totally understandable.
Anyone would have been scared.
It was your first time, right?
By the way, is it okay
if I call you Prabha?
Sure.
I noticed your friends calling
you that in your chats.
Also, it's such an interesting name.
Prabhendu.
Super sweet.
I like it.
- I really like it.
- Indu!
I need the auto rickshaw
only at 11 o'clock.
I just read the notice.
Okay!
Alright, you can have
your phone back now.
I don't need it again till the night.
Anxiety?
Bipolar?
No.
Then what on earth is it?
Huh?!
I was talking to her.
It's not dry yet.
Can you please call Doctor Raphael?
That's me.
What's the matter?
So… I'm a person who performs pujas.
Three days ago,
I went to a house for a puja.
- Not a house, actually a flat, for puja--
- Stop, Stop!
Could you please move, Chechi?
- Continue.
- Like I said, I perform pujas.
Three days ago,
I went to a flat for a puja.
It was meant to drive out a spirit.
His parents said they had
brought him to you, Doctor.
Avinash.
He's slightly chubby…
Oh, yes!
Anyway, after the puja,
he recovered completely.
But now I'm experiencing
the same symptoms he had.
I'm seeing the same girl
he said he used to see.
I saw her last night,
and again today, in broad daylight.
I could hear her voice too.
Crystal clear.
Can you see her right now?
Not right now.
And?
Well, that's all.
Also, the moment I saw that boy,
I understood what the issue was.
Seeing people who aren't there,
hearing voices nobody else hears…
Sheezo-phrenia!
Schizophrenia.
I Googled it
and I have all the symptoms.
- You Googled it?
- Yeah.
I'm willing to take any medication.
Am I talking too fast right now?
Doctor, are you following me so far?
Didn't you say you fixed
Avinash's problem with your puja?
- Yes.
- Then similarly…
why not perform a puja
and cure your own condition?
I...
I don't believe in God, Doctor.
I'm...
an atheist.
Huh?!
Then how can you be doing pujas?
Well...
I'm basically a musician.
A guitarist.
I'm on a short break right now.
I was trained in all these rituals
until I turned nineteen.
When did you begin
losing faith in this "item"?
Which "item," Doctor?
God.
Well... that...
Come with me.
One day, it was just my mother
and me at home.
My brother, father, and uncle
had gone to Delhi for a puja.
Mom and I were watching
an A.R. Rahman concert on Doordarshan.
Mom had Master's degree in Music.
She even played the veena.
We have a shrine inside the house,
almost like a small temple.
When it was time
to do the puja there,
I purified myself and went inside.
We call it the 'Thevaram'.
Just as I lit the lamp
and began the Puja,
I heard my mother
calling out to me loudly.
I ignored it.
I thought I would
finish the puja first.
When I went back,
I saw my mom lying face down
on the floor, next to the sofa.
The moment I held her,
I knew she was gone.
It was a cardiac arrest.
I held my mom in my lap
and stared right at the lamp,
still burning after the puja.
I could see it clearly
from where I was.
That day,
more than sadness,
what I felt was anger.
In that moment,
I lost my connection with God.
Man, this is your real issue!
You have deep-seated trauma.
No way.
Those two things
have nothing to do with each other.
Whether they're connected or not,
let's deal with this trauma first.
What if that girl
shows up again?
Let her show up.
She'll go away
the same way she appeared.
I'll give you a simple fix for that.
There's a tablet
that contains melatonin.
It's not a sleeping pill.
Just take it
before you go to bed.
You will get a good sleep.
Huh?
Don't I need any other medicine?
There's no better medicine in the world
than a good night's sleep.
Trust me.
You're fine.
Okay.
You are okay!
Hi!
I didn't want to wake you up,
so I just came and sat here quietly.
Anyway, I'm glad
I saw you today.
Why should we keep
startling each other like this?
We're well past that stage now,
aren't we?
Whoa! Relax.
This isn't a dream.
Look, the time is 1:40 AM.
Uncle just went to the wash room
and got back in bed.
As usual, he didn't flush.
Shall I flush it for him?
I can do it from here.
Shall I turn on the light?
Sorry, I'm just figuring this out.
You just need to change the bulb.
Indu!
I think he got up.
Tell you what.
You go back to sleep.
You've taken the medicine, right?
And if you don't mind,
I need to check some stuff on this.
I'll return it in the morning.
What was that sound?
Oh! He can't see me.
Your uncle can't see me.
Oh!
What do you mean, 'Oh'?
I asked what that sound was.
Oh, that...
I think the bulb blew
from a voltage surge.
My dear Indu,
just say your prayers
and go to sleep.
No faith in God,
but scared out of your wits!
Ugh!
Go back to sleep, Prabha.
I'm okay out here.
By the way, good call on placing
the return request for the kurta.
I ordered the white kurta
with lavender accents.
But I think they sent
white with pink instead.
Anyway, I've scheduled
the pickup for tomorrow.
Just make sure
you hand it over.
Is there something
you want to ask me?
Finally!
Go on, ask me.
Who... are you?
I hate to say this.
But I think I'm a ghost.
Yeah, I think so.
Pradeep...
July 12th and 13th
are auspicious days.
Plan it accordingly.
Okay?
What are you doing here
at this hour?
What's in the bag?
Psst... psst!
Don't! Don't!
[chants slokas]
Psst... psst!
Over here!
Where did you see it?
In my room.
- It's still here.
- Still there?
Why didn't you tell me
this when you called?
- But my phone is with her!
- Oh.
Come on.
Will she hurt me?
- I don't think so.
- You don't "think" so?
Why is this door locked?
So she can't get out.
Oh.
The ghost? Seriously?
Open it.
And that?
Open that too!
She's gone!
Didn't I tell you, Indu?
It's just your mind playing tricks.
The rest will sort itself
out after the puja.
You know who's doing it, right?
East should be this side, right?
- That side.
- Right.
No, I'll handle this.
Right now, you're the client.
- You've got a lamp?
- Yes.
Bring it here.
I need to light it.
I'll handle that as well.
Once you conquer fear,
the battle is half-won...
Hey! Where are you off to?
You asked me to bring the lamp.
Don't go alone.
I'll come with you.
Oil, coconut, matches…
Take everything at once.
Don't keep going in and
out while I'm inside.
It isn't safe.
What are you staring at?
Let's go!
My god, I've never
seen anyone so scared!
Phew! Safe!
Uncle, I've come to collect
a parcel for return.
What parcel?
It's a kurta set.
But nobody in this
house wears kurtas.
This one is a ladies' kurta.
Prabhendu must be your son, right?
- Yes.
- Ah, he ordered it.
- Here you go.
- Right!
Indutty gave it to
me in the morning.
Valentine's Day is
around the corner, right?
Must be a gift for someone special.
Oh dear, this Indutty!
Phew!
I'm not just saying this
because I did it...
- What?
- The puja was a big success.
Hmm.
That thing you spoke about…
She's a real terror.
I watched her leave
with my own eyes!
Hmm.
I'm thinking maybe
I should see that doctor again.
Come on!
What for?
This is a form of treatment too.
This time, I decided to add
a touch of extra sorcery,
just for flavour.
And it worked perfectly.
Why do you look so unconvinced?
No, I'm not doubting anything.
Alright then! Get up.
Oh my...
Let me know once you're
done being scared.
There are a few pending pujas.
Let's wrap those up too.
Alright then, I'll get going.
- Okay.
- I forgot something.
Your father is upset that you
don't visit the temple anymore.
At least go once in a while.
Poor soul.
What are you thinking?
That item?
She's gone!
Chill! Okay?
Let me see how she
dares to return now!
Okay.
Huh!
Done getting shocked?
Who's he calling an "item"?
Do I look like an item?
Don't go without talking to me.
If you keep running away,
that's all you'll ever do.
Listen... have I done anything to you
like those horror-movie ghosts?
Yes or no?
No.
Other than you getting
shocked seeing me
and me getting shocked
seeing you,
have I troubled you in any way?
Yes or no?
No.
Look, I don't have
clarity on this either.
I don't even know what happened to me.
And... I have no clue
why I'm following you around
as if we're connected
via Bluetooth.
Do you even realise
how hard this is for me?
Huh?
It's just that...
you didn't ask yes or no.
For the love of Jesus,
don't be scared of me!
It makes me feel guilty
for no reason.
Jesus?
Huh?
So, you're a Christian?
Oh! Yeah.
No wonder!
Do you sell crosses here?
What's the purpose?
For...
protection.
Protection from what?
No, no… just general safety.
Safety from what exactly?
For my own peace of mind, Chetta.
Wood or metal?
Which one is more powerful?
This isn't a light bulb
you pick by wattage.
That depends on your faith.
Lali!
Yes?
Show him the crosses.
Are you Roman Catholic?
No.
Oh, from the Jacobite Church then.
Err...
No.
Mar Thoma church, then?
Mar...
Yes.
- Huh?
- Yes, you're right.
Ah, I knew it!
The moment I saw you,
I knew you were
a proper Mar Thoma boy.
- Yes.
- Right.
So, pick whichever one
you like. Okay?
[chants slokas]
So, this should clear things up, right?
I mean, I'm literally standing
surrounded by crosses right now.
Including you.
Hey! If Jesus had a problem with me,
wouldn't I be gone by now?
Look, I honestly don't know
how I became a ghost,
or why I am one,
or how to stop being one.
And you know
what's the funny part?
I can't remember
a single important detail!
I can't even recall my name!
Answer it.
- Faizal...
- Hey, Prabha...
Wherever you are, drop everything
and get to the studio by midnight.
Viraj sir said he'll
join on a video call.
He wants to test you
for a track in his next film.
I'm kind of stuck right now.
Can we reschedule?
Don't be an idiot, Prabha!
If you miss this now,
there won't be another chance.
I've given Saadhya my word.
Stop stalling and get here.
It's 5:00 PM already.
- I'll be there.
- Okay.
I heard that.
Congrats.
Ah! Come in, come in.
I didn't take the bike,
in case it rained tonight.
Caught a direct bus.
It was pretty comfortable.
You don't mind me
eating non-veg, do you?
Not at all.
I think I'll order a dosa.
I'll order for you, man.
You haven't eaten yet?
How about podi masala dosa?
Yeah.
Who are you looking for?
Oh, nothing.
I asked if podi masala dosa is okay.
Yeah, that's fine.
Dude, hold on.
Saadhya's calling.
Hello, Saadhya...
Yeah.
He's logged in already?
No, no problem.
We're coming.
Dude, Viraj sir has already logged in.
Come on, hurry up!
What about my dosa?
I'm ditching my biriyani, and you're
worried about your dosa? Move!
Prabha, ready.
He's here.
Hi Faizal. All good?
Hi, sir. All good, sir.
All good.
The guitarist. Is he ready?
What's his name?
Prabhendu, sir.
Prabhendu.
Shall I call him here, sir?
No, no. No need.
I can hear what he plays, right?
Yeah, of course. Of course.
Okay then.
Let's start now.
Hey...
Sir has composed a new track.
He needs a guitar groove for it.
Kill it!
Faizal, I need a catchy
riff for the melody.
Yes, sir. Yes, sir.
Prabha... 2-bar cue.
Yeah, okay.
No, no.
Stop, stop.
Prabhendu, I don't want that.
It's not sounding good.
Try some strumming.
Prabha, don't try anything
too fancy.
Just stick to your comfort zone.
Okay.
No, no, no.
What are you doing, man?
Feel the melody and try again.
Faizal, give him a shorter cue.
Sure. Sure, sir.
Prabha, what's wrong with you?
Let's go. Ready.
Okay.
Take.
Stop, stop, stop.
This is not even close!
Faizal, what is this?
I already have people in Mumbai
who play like this.
I want that magic!
We shouldn't waste our time.
Let's look for someone else.
He just can't do it.
Just follow the melody.
Huh?!
What is it, man?
Oh, it's nothing.
Prabha, focus only on the melody.
It's that simple.
Play this.
Prabha...
What do I do?
- Ready.
- Okay, man.
Sir... One last time, sir?
Okay, try.
Okay, sir.
Thank you, thank you.
Prabha, take.
Oh, nice!
I like it!
Faizal, this is exactly what I want!
Thank you, sir.
Prabha, that's brilliant.
Stick with that.
Super. Add one more layer.
Faizal, turn up the reverb.
I'll add one more layer.
Ready!
Too good, man!
Continue!
Too good!
Faizal, call him!
I want to see him.
Sure, sir.
Prabha, come over here.
Sir wants to see you.
You killed it, man!
You just made the tune better,
Prabhendu.
We will do the full song together
in Mumbai.
Thank you, sir.
Perfect!
Faizal, I'll ask Saadhya to coordinate.
Okay.
Your destination is on the left.
Hey! Kiddo!
Hey, look at that.
To be honest,
I didn't quite get that initially.
Great!
And then?
That's exactly what I was thinking.
I know music, and I know
how guitar chords work.
Oh Jesus!
Kuttoos was a guitarist too!
Music connects the three of us!
Strange!
Also, you're an acoustic guy?
Electric Guitar is my favourite.
But people like Viraj sir
usually prefer acoustic
when they're composing.
Ah, I see.
Looks like you've lost your
fear and found some guts.
The fear is gone,
but the confusion remains.
Just relax, Prabha.
I think I'm just delulu.
Alright. So, delulu...
Ordering things online--